<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Miguel Outdoors</title>
    <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Miguel Outdoors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://migueloutdoors.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Art Prints</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/products-and-services/art-prints/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 18:14:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/products-and-services/art-prints/</guid>
      <description>Art Prints Maybe one day I&amp;rsquo;ll start selling prints. The first print I make will be for the first painting I&amp;rsquo;ve been proud of that was completely original plein aire. See below.
More coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Update</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2022-06-15-general-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2022-06-15-general-update/</guid>
      <description>What I&amp;rsquo;m up to nowadays I started practicing gymnastic rings way more (Check it out)! I made a couple posts and am having fun on Instagram making content. Although I will admit that I do often get absolutely sucked in to just watching memes or inspirational reels 😆. But that&amp;rsquo;s what this site is for! To get off of there and on to somewhere where I have more control.
As a part of these rings, I&amp;rsquo;ve also been exploring circus culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grip-it Rope Comp 2022</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2022-04-11-grip-it-rope-comp-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2022-04-11-grip-it-rope-comp-2022/</guid>
      <description>Post Comp I don&amp;rsquo;t know what day it is, but it&amp;rsquo;s the day after the comp. I really liked it. It felt really good to be an athlete, to feel like an athlete. I had a lot of performance, anxiety and fear when I first showed up. All the problems seemed surprisingly, not too crazy, but I kind of knew that they were sneakily hard. When we got to the first problem, I said, I had also told myself to treat it like a fun exhibition of my skills, the body, hanging out with all my friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hehe, Long Time No See</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2021-9-30-long-time-no-see/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2021-9-30-long-time-no-see/</guid>
      <description>I was really excited that I could make this website. But as soon as it was up and it came time to write, a whole new challenge became apparent to me. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say I&amp;rsquo;m a writer, so actually making posts on this website presents a scary challenge 😖.
Well I&amp;rsquo;m back! I think I&amp;rsquo;ve found a way to make writing a bit easier. As the tech entrepreneurs say, I&amp;rsquo;ve &amp;ldquo;updated my workflow&amp;rdquo; to make it so that I can do the bulk of this writing on my phone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Cat Ulee</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2021-5-13-my-cat-ulee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2021-5-13-my-cat-ulee/</guid>
      <description>This adorable little monster is my cat Ulee (OO-lee). He&amp;rsquo;s a rescue cat that I got when I was having a hard time with mental health about 2 years ago here in Norfolk. At the time, I thought that maybe some kind of emotional support animal would be good for my health.
Now, some people might say that it&amp;rsquo;s not a good idea to get an animal when you&amp;rsquo;re in that kind of place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My mini Burning Man 2022</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2022-09-06-my-mini-burning-man-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2022-09-06-my-mini-burning-man-2022/</guid>
      <description>I Loved It.
I recently decided that going to burning man is a goal. That getting there will be a project. And that while the ultimate goal is to get there eventually, I am currently more focused on the process of getting there. I almost had a chance to get a ticket this year. But I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel I was ready just yet. Instead, when the opportunity to have a small burning party came up I immediately sprang into action and started to work on building a Man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Recent Fascination With Plants 🌱</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2021-11-29-my-recent-fascination-with-plants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2021-11-29-my-recent-fascination-with-plants/</guid>
      <description>It all sort of when I accidentally took too many spider plants from a free buy nothing event in my local area. I was supposed to be two spider plants ended up being two bottles of saplings. And, lo and behold, two or three months later I now have 12 spider plants in my living room. But that&amp;rsquo;s just the beginning&amp;hellip;
I have purchased an app, orders pots and started reading as much as I could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Update 2023</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2023-03-08-winter-update-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2023-03-08-winter-update-2023/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to write here anymore. There are so many things going on in life and it feels like we&amp;rsquo;ll never have the time to fully process it all. Timelines, projects, shows, and everything else that life has to throw at you. Lots of things that could be considered good and lot of things that could be considered bad. I am overwhelmed, and this is how I&amp;rsquo;m feeling, and that&amp;rsquo;s okay.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
