<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Miguel Outdoors</title>
    <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Miguel Outdoors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://migueloutdoors.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Web Development</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/products-and-services/web-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 21:47:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/products-and-services/web-development/</guid>
      <description>Do you like this website? Thanks so much, I built it myself you know. At this time I only know how to do create static sites. And, my availability to do</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Prints</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/products-and-services/art-prints/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 18:14:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/products-and-services/art-prints/</guid>
      <description>I do not intent to make this a priority. In fact, as much as possible I&amp;rsquo;d prefer to NOT commodify my art. However, we live in the real world and if passive income can be made that can help fund other decommodified art, then maybe this is okay. If you like my art and would like a print, I made them available for you. However, I&amp;rsquo;d encourage you to check out this Wikipedia article that talks about decommodification in more detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bucket of Black Paint</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/bucket-of-black-paint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 16:50:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/bucket-of-black-paint/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m slowly taking my art more seriously. At first it was just me having fun with what I had or what I could get cheaply at Michaels. I ended up with a pretty basic plein aire paint kit that, while I do enjoy and love, has me limited to a specific size and format. From the very beginning I wanted to try and grow in scale. To practice larger format art just because it looks cool!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Is Here</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/spring-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 20:20:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/spring-is-here/</guid>
      <description>I have a little bit of an itch in my eye. The pollen is making my eyes water a whole bunch right now. But that&amp;rsquo;s a small price to pay for all of this new life. I love seeing it, the color of new live everywhere you look. I love the light greens, the pinks, the whites. There is still a lot I need to learn about winter, but I&amp;rsquo;ll worry about that in 8 months!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MiniBurn</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/gallery/miniburn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 12:35:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/gallery/miniburn/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m proud of this one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Even is Miguel?</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/who-is-miguel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 09:50:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/who-is-miguel/</guid>
      <description>I was born in Mexico and raised for the most part in Norther Virginia. When I graduated college I moved to Norfolk, Virginia. The idea was that if I was going to be an engineer, I might as well be one near the beach! 🏖️ Living here has been an absolute treat. I&amp;rsquo;ve had so many opportunities to grow. But only the future knows if I will stay.
Reading List Here&amp;rsquo;s my current reading list as well as a list of books I might want to read someday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Hugo Migration</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/the-great-hugo-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 18:20:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/the-great-hugo-migration/</guid>
      <description>Long story short, I was not having fun using Ghost as my website provider. So I left! But migrating an entire site, no matter how small, is an absolute pain in the ass. So, if you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, it means I finished. And it only took me about 3 days 😅😅😅</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drone Services</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/products-and-services/fenix-aerial-llc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 17:43:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/products-and-services/fenix-aerial-llc/</guid>
      <description>I am a FAA Part 107 Commercial Drone Pilot. Let me fly for you! Services include: photography, videography, home inspections, and more is on the way.
My Experience I&amp;rsquo;ve flown for about two years with my current job but do not have a portfolio since it&amp;rsquo;s their intelectual property.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Update 2023</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/winter-update-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/winter-update-2023/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to write here anymore. There are so many things going on in life and it feels like we&amp;rsquo;ll never have the time to fully process it all. Timelines, projects, shows, and everything else that life has to throw at you. Lots of things that could be considered good and lot of things that could be considered bad. I am overwhelmed, and this is how I&amp;rsquo;m feeling, and that&amp;rsquo;s okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My mini Burning Man 2022</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/my-mini-burning-man-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/my-mini-burning-man-2022/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m too lazy to re-upload pictures for this again. Sorry. - M 2023-03-17
I recently decided that going to burning man is a goal. That getting there will be a project. And that while the ultimate goal is to get there eventually, I am currently more focused on the process of getting there. I almost had a chance to get a ticket this year. But I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel I was ready just yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;m Up To Nowadays</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/what-im-up-to-nowadays/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/what-im-up-to-nowadays/</guid>
      <description>I started practicing gymnastic rings way more (Check it out)! I made a couple posts and am having fun on Instagram making content. Although I will admit that I do often get absolutely sucked in to just watching memes or inspirational reels 😆. But that&amp;rsquo;s what this site is for! To get off of there and on to somewhere where I have more control.
As a part of these rings, I&amp;rsquo;ve also been exploring circus culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grip-it Rope Comp 2022</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/grip-it-rope-comp-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/grip-it-rope-comp-2022/</guid>
      <description>Post Comp I have no idea what day it is, but its the day after the comp. I really liked it. It felt really good to be an athlete, to feel like an athlete. I had a lot of performance, anxiety and fear when I first showed up. All the problems seemed surprisingly, not too crazy, but I kind of knew that they were sneakily hard. When we got to the first problem, I said, I had also told myself to treat it like a fun exhibition of my skills, the body, hanging out with all my friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Recent Fascination With Plants 🌱</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/my-recent-fascination-with-plants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/my-recent-fascination-with-plants/</guid>
      <description>No Pictures here either. oh well
It all sort of when I accidentally took too many spider plants from a free buy nothing event in my local area. I was supposed to be two spider plants ended up being two bottles of saplings. And, lo and behold, two or three months later I now have 12 spider plants in my living room. But that&amp;rsquo;s just the beginning&amp;hellip;
I have purchased an app, orders pots and started reading as much as I could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hehe, Long Time No See</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/hehe-long-time-no-see/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/hehe-long-time-no-see/</guid>
      <description>I was really excited that I could make this website. But as soon as it was up and it came time to write, a whole new challenge became apparent to me. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say I&amp;rsquo;m a writer, so actually making posts on this website presents a scary challenge 😖.
Well I&amp;rsquo;m back! I think I&amp;rsquo;ve found a way to make writing a bit easier. As the tech entrepreneurs say, I&amp;rsquo;ve &amp;ldquo;updated my workflow&amp;rdquo; to make it so that I can do the bulk of this writing on my phone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Cat Ulee</title>
      <link>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2021-5-13-my-cat-ulee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://migueloutdoors.github.io/blog/2021-5-13-my-cat-ulee/</guid>
      <description>too old for retrieving images. we must move forward to todays news!
This adorable little monster is my cat Ulee (OO-lee). He&amp;rsquo;s a rescue cat that I got when I was having a hard time with mental health about 2 years ago here in Norfolk. At the time, I thought that maybe some kind of emotional support animal would be good for my health.
Now, some people might say that it&amp;rsquo;s not a good idea to get an animal when you&amp;rsquo;re in that kind of place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
